Cancer is such a treatment that if someone has a
friend at home, then someone knows, his family member knows
how costly cancer treatment is, so
friends, on today's video, I urge all of you to
share your voice,
what is the benefit, how much premium will have to be paid, it is
given in the biggest policy, then the video starts,
cancer care
75 years, that means you will do this cancer care policy,
your minimum term will be 50
years and the maximum is
75 years, the
minimum policy term is 10 years in this policy
and 30 years in the maximum policy,
if you are going to do this policy, then you should do it by
selecting any one year from 10 years to 30 years,
right, and if you
want to take a cancer care policy, then at this time
you will have to pay 50 plus 25 years, if
you are taking the premium for 20 years, then
you will have to pay for 20 years, right, and along with this, the
minimum term in this policy is
₹300000,
you can do this from 10 to 50 lakhs.  You can take a policy
and this one which I have in the red colour shirt in front, there is
a difference in this also, so
sesame policy means if
you get a diagnosis at the age of 20 then you will get a benefit of 20 lakhs,
right, if you do this for this, for example, suppose
you have increased 20 lakhs, then
see, every five years your benefit will keep increasing by
10% and from 5 years
till then your benefit will remain stable, like
see, from 20 lakhs it becomes 22 lakhs, that means 10% 24
lakhs, by doing this the number will come to six, right now
we are looking at the future of this
policy, so friends, after getting a
diagnosis you will get payment through link
or through, right, so friends, you all know that
cancer occurs in two stages, one is normal,
early stage cancer and the stage of early stage
cancer is called,
but for example, the
premium will be
25% off the semester, so okay, if it does not get cured then that
straight cancer, right, it will turn into
major stage cancer later, so what will happen to it,
you have taken 25% off the semester first  He will also get 75%
option, sir, if he is late with 20 lakhs, then he will get 75%
i.e. 15 lakhs along with the major stage
cancer detection,
friends, if cancer is removed in major stage, then it will allow to
reduce it later.
[Sangeet]
So friends, this was the benefit of this policy,
if the person gets infected, then
you are paying 25% and a small example premium for 10 years and you will get tax of 20 lakhs
and along with this, his net premium,
if the person is healthy, then it is fine, that is,
5 lakhs out of 20 lakhs will be given in advance and 15
lakhs will be paid to him.
[Sangeet] When his death occurs,
his nominee will be taken care of
and will keep giving remaining
20 lakhs, here he will get a benefit of 24 lakhs i.e. 44 lakhs
and along with this,
you will also get 44 lakhs. [Sangeet] So friends, you should take this 44 lakhs
because its premium
is very low and the benefit is high, even if you get cancer,
you will  You will get
a lump sum amount for treatment and
this is what
you will have to pay for the policy. If you get cancer today or tomorrow, the
waiting period is mentioned in it and
you will get the claim after 180 days of getting cancer and along with this, there will be a
policy for taking the
policy.
If you want to know the premium,
how much does it cost, you can
write it in the comment box. Next,
Rameshwar will write ₹3 lakh to 15 lakh and
you will write for how many years you are taking the policy, then
I will reply to you. So,
if you do not show up at the time of taking this policy,
you will have to be careful if you take the cancer policy and
in the benefit, I would like to tell you that there is no return in this policy
and no match. Hello,
any loan is not available in this policy,
you get 30 minutes.